Yes friend, my team has
edited a video and given it to me after a year, which we had recorded last
December when I was doing a show in New York,
so this video should have come
much earlier, they
cut the reel from it and put it on the ina but did
not give the video to me, but now it has come,
finally no problem, I have such a wonderful team,
so now you can watch this video and I
am touring Canada again in May, so
those who could not come to the show last time, they should
come and meet me this time, those who
live in US Canada, they will relate more to
these jokes, those who do not live
there.  If you want to go sometime, you will be
able to relate.  And those people who don't even have any chance of
going there, you are very
empty.  You can listen to the video comfortably.  So
enjoy the thing.
Firstly, you guys keep sending such messages that
come to US, come to Canada, who will tell you that you should
not come in this season.
Like after getting such a haircut, the wind hit the temples.
What kind of road is this, man?  Where is
everyone going?  [laughs] I
put on a hoodie in the cold, I couldn't move my head.  The
feet are just moving.
[Praise] I am going to
visit you like in the movie Bhagam Bhag.   It's
so cold, brother.  How are you guys doing?   My
respect for you has increased a lot.  [laughter]
And you're still living in a city like this.   There
is some excitement.  Those poor people living in
Detroit.
[laughter]
Oh child of the wretched [laughter]
Rale
Bhai, the city is so poisonous, don't go there,
we can't find the road, there's no one around,
ask who is making you wander around
in this cold, it's been more than a month, you
took me to Calgary, I'm in
Calgary
[laughter]
-25,
tell me first of all what does the bastard feel like
[applause]
I will decide that
I am dying.  [laughter]
She also tells me up front that it must be so cold.
And when someone comes for a day and
tells you that he is feeling cold, don't talk nonsense
that you should look ahead
[praise]
I am feeling cold now, why should I
look ahead [laughter] They
took me to -25, there is ice on the balcony,
I went out, I said will you take a cup, he said
in April [laughter] he
said brother, I am asking on hourly basis,
I wanted to smoke cigarettes
[laughter]
looking at the policemen here, it seems
something is wrong.  [laughs] Now I don't know,
looking at him I feel like I must have done something wrong.
Maybe they found out today.   Either
one or something different is going on in the
system a little bit.  These people do not behave very politely.
Either this is happening due to cold.
[laughter]
That everyone's intelligence has settled down.
Rest, because of this etiquette, they have become so good that
they
talk and do things so well.  Dont know
why.  Why do they smile when they look at me from the front
?  [laughter] I didn't understand it at first.
Why are you laughing at me?  And they are
greeting like this because
we cannot do all this.  No, I can't learn this, I am passing in front of you, how are you doing
your work, you sisterfucker.
[laughs]
I don't talk to my relatives, I'll hit
you in the face.
And I took this habit with me and went back to Delhi.
And I smiled at someone without any reason.
He will take me home.  [laughs]
That you keep laughing with me.
[laughs] The
police were so polite, they stopped our car, at
one point he came to the side and said, Sir, do I have
your license, please.  [laughter] I
said slap it in there.
What are you doing?  Sir, please, these are our
words, right?
When we see a policeman, we say, Sir
please
[praise]
firstly, that policeman has so much stuff on him that
how does he remember what all he has, he has
so many things on him, if
I were his policeman, one thing of mine would be left at home every day
[laughter]
that I have arrested you, on your knees the handcuffs are left
brother
[praise]
[laughter]
I am bringing them.  Don't move, remember to
stay like this.   He is
roaming around with handcuffs.  Are you mad
?  Walk around comfortably with it, hand in hand.  This is how it is
done in India.   There are
no handcuffs.  Thieves get caught hand in hand.
Then we also cooperate.  I sweat profusely.
Leaving your reach back to five.
And go on a date.
Ok.  Let's do a show.  I will
drink hot water in between.  Put it in some story.  I was
drinking something about votes.  Okay, right?
And the doctor has told me to do this.
What happens with this?  I don't know at all.   It
got cold.   No
problem, I am here with you
in this.  Firstly, you guys pay a lot of
money dollar for dollar, man.  Your respect increases a lot here.
I
bought it from New Zealand.  This is for ₹3000.  Since then
I sleep with it.
A man sits here in Delhi and heats water for ₹3000.  [laughter]
[praise] The
doctor told me that if you keep drinking hot water like this in
between the shows, it will be fine.
Last December, I lost my voice. I was
touring somewhere in Rajasthan. When I returned to
Delhi, I could not hear it. I said, it's okay, it will come back
when it comes. After two-three days,
I realized that I don't know anything else, I can't hear it. If I
call you on the show and tickle you, I wo
n't like it.
I consulted a doctor and came to Delhi.
My faith in the doctor was lost.
I said I am unable to speak and they are saying remain
silent for seven days.  [laughter]
What kind of treatment is that?  He is saying that if you remain silent for seven days, it will
come automatically.  I said okay.
I also thought that she will come.  Now friend, I don't
live alone in Delhi.  I forgot
how it was to live with my parents.  If he
comes to stay at home, we will serve him.  I
said
he comes into the house and messes with things.
Why are you messing with stuff?  How do I tell mom?
Every loose item in my house is astray.
And the vomit that is kept is full.
Firstly, parents do not realise that their children have
grown up.  I have a sore throat.  I am sleeping.  He
applied Vicks on my chest and left.
Brother, try applying Vicks to this much hair once.
[Praise]
I have been roaming around with a hot chest for three days.
The throat got cured.  My heart sank.
Hey, why did you bring such a small child?
What do you want his first words to be?
That I said mother but did not stop at mother.  [laughter]
Come on, sit down and put the phone down quietly.   This
is a live show, recording is not allowed.  Ok
?  I will pour it myself when I have to.  Anyway, nothing is going to happen
with your phone.
Your story has been liked.
Stay after the show.  I will
scatter the photos.  Ok?  I have to put that, I have to
put that.   There is
no need for any appreciation in this.
I have no work in life.   This is
my last show.  I want to go back to India.  I'm done
brother, from here.
Yes.  Such people think that after the show, they might be
partying in some unknown underground place.  [laughs] I got asked by a guy
one day after New York.  He is saying,
brother, where will you go from here to party
?  I said, listen to me.  I have
two bags with me.  One is 17 kg, one is 30
kg.  I have to do both 24.
[Applause]
So [laughter] all my focus is there.  Ok
?   That's all the
work I have.
Now, don't make up any stories in between.
I also get distracted by that.  Plus my
team is here to shoot lasers at you.
If you see this red laser rotating.   For this
I have brought a boy
from India.  Ok?  But the problem is that
in India, people don't stand at one place in the auditorium.
They shoot lasers at a guy.  The entire
auditorium is covered.  Because that
laser goes very far.
They snatched this and that from us here.  They are saying it is
not allowed.  People become blind because of this.
So ask in India that brother, shoot laser.   He is
saying shoot me.   So
now the one we have bought is the Happy
Birthday one.  Ok?  So it does
n't go very far.  And there is some very dangerous
thing brother.  Yes.  Tell me, is there a patient in this ambulance that
is moving around?
Or they just take it out to make you feel sad.  If
someone is sleeping with the window open by mistake,
he should be woken up immediately.
Someone had a heart attack and he made him sit down.
He will die from the sound.
Firstly, people also have no manners.  The ambulance is
coming.  Giving him space.
Ignore it.
In Delhi, boys follow you.  They will go faster.
I am walking a lot, friend.
I have never walked so much in my life.
Firstly, I find this red light so cute.
I think it will be green and will
do this and that.
[laughter]
But I want to go now I'm done.
I am not able to sleep here.  Have
they built these houses out of thermocol?
Brother, I slept downstairs.  My team walked up.   There is a thumping sound
going on my chest on the stairs.
[praise]
Doors are installed throughout the house.  When they
open like this.
[laughter] I've
seen such a thing in two months.
Moved to Texas.  There came the damn Amber Alert.   I do
n't know the point of any of us
sitting in a restaurant carrying such big bags.  While we were
eating, everyone's
phones suddenly rang.  The child was kidnapped.
And we have two such big bags.
Everyone is looking at us.  We said it's a
jacket.  Look at the jacket,
who knows where the child got up from.  [laughter]
You're still doing fine, man.  You can at least
talk decently.  I do
n't know who has reached Australia.  Brother,
I met a boy in a strange place.  I might meet someone
on the way, but he might not understand
who I am.  Let's say anything.
Call it comedy, call it film, call it YouTube
, anything.  Found a boy.  He is saying, Paaji,
you are the one who takes the mic and shouts.   I
said I will be the same if you agree.
I give sermons.
[Laughter]